PAULAMI CHAKRABORTY



CONTENT SOLUTIONS



WORK EXPERIENCE

2020 – PRESENT

Manager, Product Content | Dream11

Maintaining and growing **DAU**, **revenue** from communications, and **feature adoption and retention** through **paid/unpaid campaigns**, **A/B testing**, and product-led interactions.

2017 - 2020

Associate, Content & Social Media | Sportz Interactive

Planning and executing social media campaigns for leading brands including Hotstar, Delhi Capitals, UP Yoddha, and Ultimate Table Tennis.

2015 - 2017

Writer & reporter | ZEE (CricketCountry)

Producing cricket articles and news, covering live events and writing reports, and managing social media channels.



EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science, Physics major

2011 - 2014



PERSONAL SKILL

Content

Creative ideation

Audience insight





ABOUT ME

COPY AND COFFEE - BANKING ON THESE TWO FOR THE PAST 10 YEARS, I'VE BEEN PROVIDING CREATIVE SOLUTIONS FOR THE VARIOUS BRANDS AND PRODUCTS I HAVE WORKED ON.

MY MOTIVATION LIES IN THINKING FROM A USER'S POV WHILE ALIGNING WITH BUSINESS GOALS.

I AM KNOWN AS THE MOST OUT-OF-THE-BOX THINKER IN THE TEAM, AND AM DRIVEN BY DATA-BACKED RESULTS (AS WELL AS OCCASIONAL APPLAUSE FROM MY PEERS).

